我的天啊，我们真的那么做了
Oh,my God,we did it!
我们刚刚结婚了，就在那里
We just got married. Right there!
那是你的戒指吗？
Is that your ring?
我们有个不错的开始
We're off to a good start.
-你确定你没有怀孕？ -我很确定
-And,you sure you're not pregnant? -Yeah. I'm sure.
如果你准备好要生孩子 楼上有房间
But if you're ready to have kids we got a room upstairs.
我是说我会搞砸这个派对 我会那么做的
I mean,I'll blow off this party right now. I'll do it!
好了，大伙们 婚礼非常温馨
Okay,you guys,that ceremony was so beautiful.
是吗？它很完美吗？ 待会要看录影带吗？
Was it?! Was it perfect?! Is it too soon to see the video?!
大家能不能安静一分钟？ 我们两个好朋友刚刚结婚
Can we just please take a moment? Our two best friends just got married.
我们可以跟他们分享喜悦 真的非常幸运
We are so blessed to be able to share in this incredible joy.
一点都没错
That is so true.
莫妮卡，现在把鸡肉 换成牛排太晚了吧？
Mon,is it too late to switch from chicken to steak?
我为你们感到高兴 你们太幸运了
I'm so happy for you guys. And you are both so lucky!
你们叫对了彼此的名字
I mean,you both said the right names
没有人喝醉
And nobody was drunk.
好吧
Okay.
没有人是同性恋
And nobody was gay.
这是你们的第一次婚姻
And on your first try.
本集播出：婚礼之后
The.One.After.I.Do
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
主演：寇妮考克斯
主演：丽莎库卓
主演：麦特勒布兰
主演：马修派瑞
主演：大卫修蒙
太棒了 让我换一下底片
Great. Great. Just give me a sec to change film.
我知道你不希望我知道 但我知道了，我为你感到高兴
I know I'm not supposed to know,but I do and I'm so excited for you.
-发生了什么事？ -莫妮卡怀孕了
-What's going on? -Monica's pregnant.
天啊 所以你们两个要结婚？
Oh,my God. Is that why you guys had to get married?
-听着，我没有怀孕 -精子游得太慢了？
-Guys,I'm not pregnant. -Oh,slow swimmers?
什么？你是什么意思？ 你没有怀孕？
What?! What do you mean? You're not pregnant?
-你没有告诉任何人我怀孕了吧？ -没有
-You didn't tell anybody I was,did you? -No.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
你，多拍一些照片
You. Take a lot of pictures.
我们为什么不拍张 莫妮卡跟英勇士兵的合照？
Why don't we get a shot of Monica and the bloody soldier.
关于那一点，乔伊 你得在婚宴开始前换套衣服
About that,Joey,you have to change before the party.
-我办不到，我没带衣服来换 -拜托你去找套衣服
-I can't. I don't have any other clothes here. -Find some,please.
别再穿着 “我在法国战死”的衣服
Anything that doesn't say,"I died tragically in France."
-好吧 -不要乱抱任何人，好吗？
-Fine! -And be careful who you hug,okay?
我爸在楼上哭得半死 因为你害他的礼服沾到了血
My father's upstairs in tears because you got blood on his dress.
我们为什么不让新人 跟伴娘们合照一些照片？
Why don't we see the bride and the groom,and the bridesmaids.
莫妮卡，你为什么告诉大家 你没有怀孕？
Hey,Mon,why'd you tell the guys that you weren't pregnant?
-因为我没有怀孕 -我们发现了你的验孕棒
-Because I'm not. -We found your tests.
如果你没有怀孕…
If you're not pregnant..
那是因为我怀孕了
it's because I am.
你在胡说什么？
What are you talking about?
对，我怀了孩子
Yes,I am with child.
我不想说 因为今天是你们的大喜之日
I didn't want to say anything because it's your day.
-我不想抢了你的风采 -于是你告诉大家我怀孕了？
-I didn't wanna steal your thunder. -So you told people I was pregnant?
这是那种 我会想记住的对话吗？
Does this look like a conversation I want to remember?
-孩子的爸是谁？ -对
-Who's the father? -Yeah.
我不能说
I can't say.
-为什么？ -为什么不行？
-Why? -Why not?
我不能说，因为他是名人
I can't say because he's famous.
天啊，他是谁？
Oh,my God. Who is it?
菲比，你得告诉我们
Phoebe,come on,you have to tell us.
好吧，是詹姆斯布洛林（影星）
Okay,okay,it's James Brolin.
詹姆斯布洛林是孩子的爸爸
James Brolin is the father of my baby.
你是说芭芭拉史翠珊的老公 詹姆斯布洛林？
As in Barbra Streisand's husband James Brolin?
什么？
What?!
他一直都没有告诉我
Well,he never said that to me.
莫妮卡，请你先离开 我们要拍钱德跟伴娘的合照
Monica,if you step away,we'll get Chandler and the bridesmaids.
何不只拍伴娘的合照呢？
How about just the bridesmaids?
我是新郎 听说这个位置很重要
I am the groom. I was told it was a big deal.
-没错 -对
-It is. -Yeah.
天啊
Oh,my God.
谢谢你 我还没有办法承受那样的压力
Thank you for that. I can't deal with the stress quite yet.
于是你告诉我 莫妮卡怀孕了？
Instead you told me Monica was pregnant?
是你说她怀孕了 我没有反驳你
You said she was. I didn't disagree with you.
很狡猾
Sneaky.
笑一个，小姐们
Smile,ladies!
-对了，詹姆斯布洛林？ -我知道
-By the way,James Brolin? -I know.
我脑海里浮起两个人名 他跟小艾德贝格利（影星）
I could only think of two names: him and Ed Begley Jr.
-然后我想起来他是同性恋，所以…-小艾德贝格利不是同性恋
-Then I remembered he's gay,so.. -Ed Begley Jr. is not gay.
真的吗？
Really?
恭喜
Congratulations!
看看谁结婚了 我听说你们是奉子成婚
Look who's married! And just in time too,I hear.
什么？罗斯
What? Ross!
如果你不去好好解释 我会…
So if you've got this all under control,I'm just gonna..
我只是要你知道 你让我们更快乐了
I just wanted you to know that you have made us happier
你让我们更加高兴…
You have given us more joy..
我没有怀孕
I'm not pregnant.
什么？
What?
我没有怀孕
I'm not pregnant.
好吧
Oh,well.
但我今天还是结婚了
But I did still get married today.
随便
Whatever.
谢谢
Thank you very much.
各位先生女士 我很荣幸跟大家介绍
Ladies and gentlemen,it gives me great pleasure to introduce to you:
钱德宾夫妇
Mr. and Mrs. Chandler Bing.
-到舞池前我要送你一份礼物 -我不想把手伸到你的口袋里
-Before we go out there,I got a present. -I'm not gonna put my hand in your pocket.
-不，我去上了舞蹈课 -什么？
-No. I've been taking dancing lessons. -What?
我上了六星期的舞蹈课 我希望这一刻能让你永生难忘
For the last six weeks. I wanted this to be a moment you'd never forget.
那真的是太体贴了
That is so sweet.
你愿不愿意以夫妻的身份 跟我跳第一只舞？
So would you care to join me in our first dance as husband and wife?
我愿意
Yes.
-怎么了？ -我的新鞋太滑了
-What's the matter? -It's these new shoes,they're all slippery.
-你能跳舞吗？ -不太行
-Are you gonna be able to do this? -Not well.
好消息是 我想没有人在看我们
Well,the good news is,I don't think anyone's looking at us.
你准备要谈了吗？
So are you ready to talk about it?
不
No.
现在呢？
Now?
不
No!
-我们来谈别的事 -谢谢
-We'll talk about something else then. -Thank you.
孩子的爸是谁？
Who's the father?
亲爱的，我还没有告诉他…
Honey,I haven't told him yet..
我打算先告诉他 再告诉其他人
so,until I do,I don't think I should tell anybody else.
没关系，那很公平
That's fine. That's fair.
-是泰格吗？ -菲比
-Is it Tag? -Phoebe!
好吧，对不起，我不说了
Okay,I'm sorry. I'll stop.
是罗斯吗？是罗斯吧？
Is it Ross? It's Ross,isn't it?
-天啊，是乔伊 -别说了，好吗？
-Oh,my God,it's Joey! -Stop it. Okay?
在告诉他之前 我不会告诉你的
I am not gonna tell you until I tell him.
至少我们知道他是个男的
At least we know it's a him.
天啊
Oh,sweet Lord.
对不起，好吗？ 我跑到礼品店
I'm sorry,okay? I went down to the gift shop.
那里只卖这个跟浴袍 什么事比较重要呢？
It was either this or a bathrobe. What's more important:
我的穿着打扮 还是我今天能够出席？
The way I'm dressed,or being with you today?
我不会假装 我听到你说什么
Honey,I'm not gonna even pretend I was listening. Hey! Hey!
我是罗斯，我相信我们没有见过 我是莫妮卡的哥哥
I'm Ross,I don't believe we met. I'm Monica's older brother.
我是她在餐厅的同事蒙娜
Hi,I'm Mona from her restaurant.
你好，她在餐厅的同事蒙娜
Hello,Mona from her restaurant.
蒙娜，这个名字很美
Mona. What a beautiful name.
你真的那么想？ 我一直都很讨厌这个名字
You think so? I always kind of hated it.
少来了，蒙娜丽莎
Come on! Mona Lisa.
蒙娜…
Mona...
利格拉齐
Llegglachen.
她是著名的植物学家
The famous botanist.
不，她… 她死了，但是…
Oh,no,she's.. Well,she's dead now,but..
她曾经是植物学界 最性感的女人
Supposedly she was once quite the hottie of the plant world.
真的吗？
Really?
-我根本不认识她 -琳达利格拉齐…
-See,I never knew about her. -Linda Llegglachen..
你在几号桌？
So,what table are you at?
我也是
Me too.
很好，那么有个喜欢我名字的人 会跟我同桌
Good. Now there'll be someone there who likes my name.
对，没错
Yes,there will.
猜怎么了？茉莉吉柏特 你刚刚被踢到一号桌
Guess what,Molly Gilbert. You've just been bumped up to table one.
如果你没有意见的话 我要代替你坐到六号桌
And if it's all right with you,I'll take your place at table six.
马丁利格拉齐
Martin Llegglachen.
那样子好多了，现在双手弯曲 眼睛看前方
That's better. Now,just bend your arms a little bit. Now look straight ahead.
这次我要你 臀部用力顶
This time I want you to really put your ass into it.
看你还滑不滑？
Who's slippery now?
那真的很棒吧？ 拿叉子去磨你的鞋底？
Isn't that just the best feeling? Rubbing a fork on the bottom of your shoe?
钱德，你看 我的男伴终于来了
Chandler,darling,look,my date has finally arrived.
我要你见见丹尼斯菲利浦斯 丹尼斯，他是我儿子钱德
I'd like you to meet Dennis Phillips. Dennis,this is my son,Chandler.
-恭喜 -谢谢
-Congratulations. -Thank you.
丹尼斯是我的老朋友…
Dennis is a dear old friend..
跟好情人
and a fantastic lover.
我的耳朵在流血吗？
Are my ears bleeding?
别理钱德 他一向都很害羞
Don't mind Chandler. He's always been shy.
你说的对
Oh,you're right.
太棒了，丹尼斯 谢谢你取悦我老妈
Bravo,Dennis. Thanks for pleasing my mother so.
抱歉我没赶上婚礼 我忙着在试镜
I'm so sorry I missed the ceremony. I was stuck at auditions.
对，丹尼斯正在执导 一出百老汇新戏
Yes,Dennis is directing a new Broadway show.
我不敢相信能见到你 乔伊崔比亚尼
I don't believe we've met. Joey Tribbiani.
-丹尼斯菲利浦斯 -多年来我一直很仰慕你的成就
-Dennis Phillips. -I've admired your work for years.
-你真的很棒 -谢谢
-You've done some really amazing stuff. -Thank you.
对不起 我要去喝点东西
If you'll excuse me,I'm gonna go get myself a drink.
我马上回来
I'll be back in a moment.
好吧，可以停止了
Okay. You stop.
丹尼斯菲利浦斯，那真的是太棒了 你们怎么认识的？
Dennis Phillips. That's great. How did you guys meet?
-那是个有趣的故事 -是普通有趣还是爆笑？
-Well,it's a funny story. -Funny,"ha-ha"? Or funny:
谢谢，大家请坐 晚宴马上开始
Thank you. If everyone will please take your seats,dinner will be served.
-我以为你在六号桌 -不，是九号桌
-I thought you were at table six. -No. Nine.
你刚刚拿给我看时 是那样子拿的…
See,before,when you showed it to me,you held it that way..
我被你误导了
which was misleading.
你们好
Hello.
你能请你妈把我的履历表 拿给丹尼斯菲利浦斯吗？
Will you see if your mom can give my resume to Dennis Phillips?
他们正把自己 锁在男洗手间里
Well,they've kind of locked themselves in one of the men's room stalls right now.
或许等他们出来再说
Perhaps when they get out.
只要能演百老汇舞台剧 我什么戏都能演
If I could get in a Broadway show,then I would've done it all.
电影，电视剧跟舞台剧
Film,television and theater.
唯一例外是广播剧 因为那是给丑八怪演的
The only thing left would be radio. But that's just for ugly people.
-你穿几号鞋？ -11，11号半
What size shoes do you wear? -Eleven,11
我的鞋子太滑没办法跳舞 你的靴子能借我吗？
My shoes give me a problem on the dance floor. Can I borrow your boots?
我真的不知道 我把靴子丢到哪里去了
I don't really even know where I left those.
-你的脚不可能是11号半 -好吧，我穿七号的鞋子
-Those aren't 11 . -Okay,fine,I'm a 7!
我的脚非常小 但其他部份都很大，我可以露给你看
I have surprisingly small feet. But the rest of me is good. I'll show you.
我在跟谁开玩笑呢？ 我应该去演广播剧
Who am I kidding? I belong in radio.
-你能相信菲比怀孕了吗？ -现在别谈那件事
-Can you believe Phoebe got pregnant? -Let's not talk about that right now.
-这是大消息 -没错，但它没有你的婚礼重要
-This is so huge. -Sure,but as big as your wedding?
当然，我的婚礼是最重要的
Of course not. Nothing is.
这是我们私下的谈话 到了这个时代…
Between me and you,in this day and age..
谁会笨到 让自己怀孕？
how dumb do you have to be to get pregnant?
有时候你该做的都做了 大家都戴上他们该戴的东西…
Sometimes you can do everything right. Everyone wears what they're supposed to..
但有个小家伙 还是攻过了城池
and one of those little guys just gets through.
-怎么会呢？ -我不知道，或许它们有工具
-How? -I don't know. Maybe they have tools.
我跟她谈过 她想留下孩子
Well,I talked to her,and she's definitely gonna have the baby.
她说 她要自己抚养孩子
She said she's gonna raise it on her own.
-或许那真的很勇敢 -或许吧
-Well,maybe that's really brave. -Maybe.
我只是希望 她知道那有多辛苦
I just hope she realizes how hard it's gonna be.
或许她没有 想那么多
Maybe she hasn't really thought it through that much.
的确有很多事需要考虑
Well,there's a lot to think about.
她要怎么处理经济问题？ 她怎么有办法去工作？
How is she gonna handle this financially? How is she gonna juggle work?
她知道她在未来的18年内 都无法再去约会了吗？
Does she realize she's not gonna have a date again for the next,like,18 years?
我不知道
I don't know.
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
我只是想到了菲比 怀了孕的可怜菲比
I'm just thinking about Phoebe. Poor,knocked-up Phoebe.
-要喝香槟吗？ -好的，谢谢你
-Champagne? -Oh,yes! Thank you very much.
法国人都是那样喝香槟的
That's actually how the French drink it.
我刚刚跟我的情人 詹姆斯布洛林通过电话
Well,I just got off the phone with my lover James Brolin.
-真的吗？ -很明显地他娶了一个歌手
-Oh,really? -Apparently,he is married to some singer.
但他说他会为了我离开她 我说“詹姆斯布洛林，你确定吗？”
But he said he'd leave her for me. And I said,"James Brolin,are you sure?"
-詹姆斯布洛林说… -怀孕的人是瑞秋？
-James Brolin said.. -Rachel's the one who's pregnant?
什么？
What?!
干嘛那么麻烦呢？
Why bother?
-你觉得如何？ -我不知道我有什么感觉
-How do you feel? -I don't know how I feel.
一切发生的太快 我得做出这些我不想做的决定
This is all happening so fast. I have to make all these decisions that I don't wanna make.
快把这玩意拿走
Someone just take this away from me!
-冷静点，或许你没有怀孕 -什么？
-Calm down. Maybe you're not pregnant. -What?!
我怀三胞胎时 也验了三次孕才确定
When I got pregnant with the triplets,I took that test,like,three times.
对，或许是假警报 你确定你尿在验孕棒的方式没错？
Yes. Maybe it's a false positive. Are you sure you peed on the stick right?
不然我要怎么尿才对？
How many ways are there to do that?
我是说没有百分之百确定前 别大惊小怪
I'm just saying,don't freak out until you're 100 percent sure.
好吧 我回家后会再验一次
All right,I'll take it again when I get home.
我可以等到那时候再说
I can wait until then.
这个派对很棒 它什么时候会结束？
Oh,this is such a good party. How late does it go till?
-你可以现在验 -不，这是你的婚礼
-You gotta take it now. -No,this your wedding.
没有确定前你根本无法尽兴地玩 就把它当成送我的礼物吧
You're not gonna be able to have fun until we know. Do it as a present to me.
好吧，谢谢你
Okay,thank you.
-我去帮你买验孕棒 -你们真的是太棒了
-I'll run out and get you one. -You girls are so great.
-等一下，孩子的爸是谁？ -她不肯告诉我们
-Wait a minute. Who's the father? -She won't tell us.
快说吧，这是我的婚礼 你可以当做是送我的礼物
Come on! It's my wedding. That could be my present!
-我刚刚答应为了你验孕 -看吧，这就是你注册结婚的原因
-I just gave you peeing on a stick. -See,this is why you register.
又是椅子的声音，好吗？ 不是我干的
It was the chair again. Okay? I'm not doing it!
爸爸，你不能回你的桌子去吗？
Dad. Can't you go back to your table?
不，很明显地小茉莉吉柏特 正开心地吃她的大号鲑鱼开胃菜
No. Apparently little Molly Gilbert is enjoying her grown-up salmon en croute.
听着，我没有… 你知道吗？
Look,I don't.. You know what?
-你想跳舞吗？ -好啊
-Would you like to dance? -Sure.
太棒了
Great.
-盖勒博士 -我没有放屁
-Dr. Geller. -I wasn't farting!
那是我们那一桌玩的小游戏
A little game from our table.
盖勒博士，你愿意跟我跳舞吗？
Dr. Geller,will you dance with me?
或许待会再说 现在我要跟这位小姐跳舞
Maybe later. Right now,I'm about to dance with this lady.
除非这位小姐不介意 让你插队
Unless this lady wouldn't mind letting you go first.
我很乐意 你太好心了
I'd be happy to. You are very sweet.
没错
Yes,I am.
事实上我们来试试我的绝招 你可以踩在我的脚上跳舞
In fact,let's try my special way. You can dance on my feet.
-没问题 -是吗？跳上来吧
-Sure. -Yeah? Hop on.
那个美丽的小姐在看吗？ 继续跳
Is the pretty lady looking? Keep dancing.
谁看得到呢？
And the world will never know.
你跟丹尼斯提过我的事了吗？
Did you talk to Dennis about me yet?
我跟他提到你非常有天份 还有《我们的日子》的事
I told him how talented you were and all about Days of our Lives.
你不能告诉百老汇导演那种事 现在他会以为我是肥皂剧演员
You don't tell a Broadway guy that! Now he thinks I'm just a soap actor.
但你不只是肥皂剧演员
But you're not just a soap actor.
你是有双小脚的 肥皂剧演员
You are a soap actor with freakishly tiny feet.
他不知道 我有多厉害
He has no idea what kind of range I have.
别动
Don't move.
那像是他用 小脚在跑步
It's like he's running on tiny little pegs.
-谢谢 -不，谢谢你，米兰达
-Thank you. -No,thank you,Miranda.
-是梅玲达 -好吧
-Melinda. -All right.
-那真的好可爱 -你在看我们吗？
-How cute was that? -Oh,were you watching?
下一个是我吗？
Can I go next?
当然是，来吧
Of course you can. Hop on.
好吧，但我要排在她后面
Okay,but I get to hop on after her.
-我一定能得分 -什么？
-I am so gonna score. -What?
我喜欢你的蝴蝶结
I like your bow.
我要请大家举杯 向莫妮卡及钱德致意…
I'd like to propose a toast to Monica and Chandler..
他们是全世界最速配的夫妻 也是我最好的朋友
the greatest couple in the world,and my best friends.
我刚听说他们要结婚时 我非常生气
When I first found out they were getting married,I was a little angry.
我心想“天啊，为什么？ 你为什么要把他们从我身边抢走？”
I was like,"Why,God? Why? How can you take them away from me!"
然后我回想起我们之间所有的回忆 快乐的回忆
But then I thought back over all our memories together. Some happy memories.
跟悲伤的回忆
And there were some sad memories.
对不起
I'm sorry.
可怕的回忆
And some scared memories.
然后我了解到 我永远都会是他们的朋友
And then I realized I'll always be their friend.
他们的朋友 能说许多台词…
Their friend who can speak in many dialects..
接受过舞台打斗训练 愿意拍部份裸露的戏
and has training in stage combat and is willing to do partial nudity.
敬这对快乐的夫妇
To the happy couple.
-谢谢 -那真的是太棒了，艾许莉
-Thank you. -That was very nice,Ashley.
-我们能再跳一次吗？ -不
-Can we do it again? -No,no.
-现在轮到我了吗？ -我是下一个
-So,is it my turn now? -I'm next.
-没关系，你可以先跟她跳 -你确定？
-That's okay,you can dance with her first. -Are you sure?
-你叫什么名字？ -葛特
-So,what's your name? -Gert.
那个名字很美
That's pretty.
你在做什么？葛特
What are you doing there,Gert?
跟其他女孩一样 踩在你脚上跳舞
Dancing on your feet like the other girls did it.
好吧
Okey
跳上来吧，葛特
Hop on,Gert.
-你的脚为什么不动？ -我在努力了
-Why aren't you moving your feet? -I'm trying.
快一点，你跳的太慢了
Faster. You're not going fast enough.
或许我该踩在你脚上
Maybe I should stand on your feet!
你有听到 我的致词了吗？
So did you happen to catch my toast up there?
-天啊，你那么做是为了我？ -我那么做是为了所有人
-Oh,my God. That was for my benefit? -There was a little something for everyone.
-我知道你在为新戏选角 -我想你不适合这个计划
-I know you're casting for this new show. -I don't think you're right for this project.
你错了
You're wrong.
不论内容是什么，我都办得到 如果你对刚刚的表演不满意，考考我
Whatever it is,I can do it. If you didn't see it up there,just try me.
那出戏的演员全是中国人 你可以变成中国人吗？（亚洲人眼睑处有“蒙古褶”）
It's an all Chinese cast. Can you be Chinese?
-我不以此为荣，但是… -天啊，求求你别那么做
-Well,I'm not proud of this,but.. -Oh,my God. Please don't!
-准备重回舞池了吗？ -它变成沙地了吗？
-Ready to get back to the dance floor? -Did it turn into sand?
-我喜欢这首歌，你会跳得很好的 -不，我不会的
-Come on,I love this song. You'll be fine. -No. No,I won't.
你知道为什么 我要去上舞蹈课吗？
Do you know why I took all those lessons?
我不希望你被看到 跟一个笨拙的白痴跳舞…
I didn't want you to be embarrassed to be seen on the dance floor..
丢光了脸
with some clumsy idiot.
亲爱的 你不可能让我出糗
Oh,sweetie,you could never embarrass me.
好吧，你很容易就会让我出糗 但那不重要，好吗？
Okay,you could easily embarrass me. But it doesn't matter,all right?
我嫁给了你
I married you.
不论你做什么 我会跟你回家，好吗？
No matter what you do,I'm gonna come home with you,okay?
我要在新婚之夜 跟我丈夫跳舞，来吧
So I'm gonna dance on my wedding night with my husband. Come on.
但我告诉你，那是我最后一次 在超滑鞋店买鞋子
But I'll tell you,that's the last time I buy shoes at the Slippery Fun Shoe store.
尽量不要移动你的脚
Just try not to move your feet at all.
就是那样
There you go.
-我要逮捕你 -为什么？
-I'm gonna have you arrested. -Why?
你偷走了我的舞步
You stole my moves!
钱德，你是跳舞高手
Oh,Chandler,you're quite the dancer!
-谢谢你，盖勒太太 -少来了，你可以叫我妈妈
-Thanks,Mrs. Geller. -Oh,come on,you can call me Mom.
真的吗？
Really?
我会的
I will.
抱歉，妈妈
Sorry,Mom.
-还要多久？ -30秒
-How much longer? -30 seconds.
30秒，好吧…
Thirty seconds,okay..
我错过了吗？
Did I miss it?
我要你知道如果是阳性反应 我们得…
I want you to know that if it's positive,we're gonna..
-我知道 -你知道，好吧
-I know. I know. -You do. Okay.
时候到了
It's time.
不准进来
No
来吧，瑞秋
Go ahead,Rach.
等一下，知道吗？我不敢看 谁帮我看一下
Wait. You know what? I can't look at it. Somebody else tell me.
是阴性反应
It's negative.
-什么？ -是阴性反应
-What? -It's negative.
是这样
Well,there you go.
那…那真的是太棒了 这真是个天大的好消息
That is.. That's great. That is really great,great news.
因为这整件事…
You know,because the whole..
在经济方面我还没有准备好 所以…
not being ready and,kind of,the financial aspects,all that..
事情本来就应该 是这样的
This is so just the way that this was supposed to be.
那么说的话，太棒了
Then,great.
天啊，这真的是太愚蠢了
God,this is so stupid.
我怎么会为了 我从来没有拥有过的东西难过？
How can I be upset over something I never had?
-是阴性反应吗？ -不，是阳性反应
-It's negative? -No,it's positive.
-什么？ -不是阴性反应，是阳性反应
-What? -It's not negative,it's positive.
-你确定？ -对，刚刚我说谎
-Are you sure? -Yeah,I lied before.
-现在你知道你真正的感觉了 -那是个危险的小把戏
-Now you know how you really feel about it. -That's a risky little game.
你真的要这么做？
Are you really gonna do this?
对
Yeah.
我要生下孩子
I'm gonna have a baby.
I'm gonna have a baby!
-孩子的爸是谁？ -不，现在还不是时候
-With who? -No,it's still not the time.
我不知道接下来是快歌
I just didn't see the fast song coming.
别说话，我们送你回房间 让你泡泡脚，你会没事的
Don't talk,we'll get you up to your room,soak your feet. You'll be okay.
-谢谢 -那真的是太好心了
-Thank you. -That is so sweet!
不，我是认真的 现在好男人不多了
No,I mean it. There are so few genuinely nice guys out there.
你说的对 我觉得自己像是死守碉堡的士兵
Tell me about it. I feel like I'm holding down the fort by myself.
-你是乔伊，对吧？ -对
-It's Joey,right? -Yeah.
等一下，不
Wait a minute! No!
我才是好人
I'm the nice one!
是我整晚跟孩子们跳舞 我…
I'm the one that danced with the kids all night. I..
你的脚好小
How small are your feet?!